- Are you dissatisfied with me?
- Yes, I am.
You are? Then tell me. I'm ready to listen.
Your daughter Hae Yoon is a great woman.
And I, your son in law, am a man of good sense.
- So?
- Trust me.
We keep fighting preparing for this wedding.
You're a big reason we always fight.
It's not just me!
You think your mom isn't part of it?
I'll talk to my mom.
Don't worry about that.
So I want you to treat me as your son in law.
The reason I was so blunt with you
is because I thought of you as a son.
- Did that bother you?
- A son-in-law can't be your son.
And a daughter-in-law can't be my mom's daughter.
Let's not be hypocritical.
Are you saying I'm hypocritical?
No. People say what they don't mean.
They say one thing but act resentful or differently.
The truth is they can't win their kids.
I know you're different from them.
So all I have to do is to trust you from now on?
Yeah.
Fine. I'll decide if I can trust you or not after you solve this problem.
I'd trust you if you were my son.
But you said you can't be my son.
How can I trust other people so easily?
I can't do that.
Then I'll set up the date again after you submit the evidence.
All rise.
So he's the new lawyer?
Hi, I'm Jun Sang Jin. Contact me when you need me.
- I'm specialized in divorce cases. - You're kind of brazen.
Not as much as you are.
I'll see you at home.
I'm not going to make food for you anymore.
Eat it at Yuri's house.
So you can take a picture of me as evidence?
Feel free to go. I already have enough pictures for the evidence.
Wait.
I'll leave the house like you want so pack my stuff.
Why do I pack your stuff? I'm not your wife anymore.
Do I have to go there only to pack my stuff?
Can't you just do it?
What are you going to tell Tae Hyun?
Do you want me to tell him?
We can tell him together.
- I'll do it first.
- Then let's do it together.
You asked me so you can do what I don't want to do, didn't you?
You're right. I'm being so gentle.
I'm warning you what I'm going to do.
It's snowing.
It's the first snow this year.
All the couples must be going crazy.
I Know.
You're a couple too. Feel bad that you're with me now.
Should I just fight with her?
She's not going to kill me though.
Who's there?
I'm calling the police.
No. I already called the police.
Why would you call the police?
It's so cold. Why didn't you open the door?
What are you doing?
You have nowhere to go. You can't sleep here.
- I'm not going to your house though.
- You're not going.
Can I not? I'm kind of scared to go to my house.
Yay.
Then let's go.
- That was so easy.
- I'm actually a very difficult man.
- What are you doing?
- I'm holding your bag.
It's okay. It's not heavy at all.
It's okay. I'll hold it.
How do you shut the door? I'll do it for you.
I should turn on the security system, right?
What are you trying to be? A prince?
How did you know? Women like that.
They like to feel protected by a man.
You like that too, don't you?
- Your heart fluttered, didn't it?
- Did you bring your motorcycle?
No. It's snowing now.
It's too dangerous to ride it now.
I didn't go through menopause yet.
You like me now? Wow, you're easy.
I didn't know how easy you are. That's not fun.
You're just like young women.
You should be different
from them since you're old.
I felt for you all of sudden.
I know how lonely you are. You're doing
this to get attention.
I'm not that great woman.
I know how that feels to be lonely.
Go first. I'll follow you
after shutting the door.
Let's start over...
with holding hands.
You're so funny. You rejected
me twice in one day.
You know what? I at least give it
a shot even if I get rejected.
You'll just be a lost soul wailing.
[Jung Hoon]
What are you doing here?
Don't get us wrong.
We met because of Dong Bi.
I didn't ask you anything.
You can go, Sang Jin.
Thank you.
You left while I went to get my car.
You're so funny.
It's kind of hard to meet all three of us like this.
Would you like a drink?
I had to go. Would I leave if it weren't that bad?
Until when are you going to do that?
Why didn't you answer my phone?
You were too happy to get the phone
because you were with him?
- What did I do wrong?
- I said you can go.
I will leave. It seems like
you two need to talk more.
You're mad again!
Fine. I got mad! I have a
clear reason why I got mad.
But what are you?
I can understand why he got mad. Let him
go tonight and talk to him tomorrow.
[Hae Yoon]
He's not answering my call.
Would you if you were him? How many times
did you ignore that bastard's calls?
I wouldn't answer the phone either.
Don't call him a bastard.
Only I can call him that.
Respect him. He's different from you.
He doesn't get mad just because
I ignored his calls and met you today.
You're making me angry. You weren't
like this when you dated me.
Why is he honking at me?
Go first then.
Stop!
Are you crazy? How could you drive like
this when a woman is sitting next to you?
I told him to do that.
You're overacting because your girlfriend is in front of you.
Do you think you're being a great man?
Even if she told you to do that,
you should've rejected it.
What if she got hurt?
This is why I don't want
to be involved in other people's drama.
I'll be a loser if I keep staying here.
I'll leave.
Are you out of your mind?
Why did you do that?
If you just leave like that,
when can I see you?
If I got mad, you don't try to
make me feel better.
And you don't answer my calls.
You had three chances.
The first one was when I asked you
where you were with the rice porridge.
The second one was when I asked
you about the ring tone.
The third one was when I asked if you knew
Sang Jin would come to Dong Bi's house.
It was all Jun Sang Jin, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was.
You didn't meet him because of Dong Bi.
You met him to get comforted
after you got yell at by my mom.
No. I really did meet him because of Dong Bi.
I even went to the police to report.
I thought he knew how to find
her since he's a lawyer.
You didn't even care if she was gone or not.
Dong Bi went to the U.S because of her brother.
She called me on the day she was gone.
Dong Bi didn't want others
to know about this.
Am I not her friend?
I can't believe her.
Why did she call you but not me?
Are you closer with her more than I am?
Maybe she feels more comfortable with me.
Why does she feel like that?
Ask Dong Bi! That's not important to me now.
It is to me!
I feel so mad!
I hate that you shared things
with her without me!
You're so self-centered.
I thought you're very
different from your mother.
But you're a lot like her.
Are you insulting my Mom right now?
What's so bad about looking after yourself?
All people tend to care about
themselves not others.
Are you looking down on my mom because
she works in a store?
I'm sure your mom lived well
in her little bubble...
But my mom is different.
My mom protected me by blocking
out the bad things in the world.
That's why she's tough.
Is that a bad thing?
She never fooled anyone when
she sold goods to others.
She never preyed on others with greed.
Loving one's kids too much is a crime?
Why do you change the subject?
We were talking about Jun Sang Jin.
You lied to me.
You lied to me habitually.
If you ignore my mom,
I'm never going to forgive you.
Sis, am I dead?
It sounds like you know me from a previous life.
My memories of the previous life disappeared after I became the angel of death.
I knew you'd become something even after you died.
You can't go to heaven since you haven't experienced a man.
What?
It's a sin if someone doesn't love anybody.
You're one of them.
Then what's going to happen to me?
You will have to wander in hell forever.
No!
Your sister sleeps at late night, doesn't she?
The light is still on!
What were you thinking about?
What's wrong?
- Can I still hold your hand?
- Yeah, you can.
Do you feel better if you play hard to get?
- I'm not going to go home tonight.
- What are you talking about?
I told you we should start from holding hands.
Then when are we going to have sex?
- What?
- Are we not sleeping together?
We will.
Why rush?
We don't know when we're going to die.
We should do it and be done with it.
What? Do what and get what done?
Did you really not sleep with a man before?
I did.
I have.
I can know if you're telling the truth or not.
A man can find out if it's the first time or not.
What should I do?
Should I tell him the truth?
I like how my heart flutters
before I sleep with somebody.
It's a very precious moment.
We can't just let it go away.
Let's enjoy everything step by step.
No! Holding hands isn't fun.
- Just go home
- No!
What are you doing?
I'm not going to go!
Just get punished by your sister.
I thinks that's a better idea.
- Don't try to seduce me.
- You hate me after I held your hand, right?
Hae Yoon.
- Hae Yoon.
- What are you doing there?
I'm going home.
- Did you meet Jung Hoon?
- Yeah. Bye.
What's wrong with her?
That was so cold.
- Don't make Mom angry.
- What did I do?
She's so stressed because of Hae Jin's divorce.
Don't make her stressed.
Hae Jin is getting a divorce?
Why?
Are you really our family?
- Sis.
- Kneel down.
Hae Yoon is here.
You know it's embarrassing.
You crazy bitch.
Why do you date a thug? How can you trust a man who rides a motorcycle?
He might die from riding that.
I don't care if he's in a gang or not.
The fact that I'm dating a man is important.
They say late bloomers are hopeless, and I see that's what happened.
So are you going to live with him?
I might or not.
I'm going to do whatever I want to.
So stop cleaning up the mess your kids made. Meet a rich man and start over!
You can't even get compliments even if you sacrificed for us.
Did you took drugs or something?
Do I take care of my kids and my sister just to get compliments?
Just leave me alone. I'm 50. There aren't many days left until I die.
So are you going to die from riding the motorcycle? Sell that thing, okay?
- No!
- Then get out!
I can't stand you riding that.
I'm not afraid of dying.
I'm afraid of living!
- Fine. I'll get out of this house.
- You're so out of your mind now.
Open the door.
Open it!
- What are you doing?
- You must be so tired.
Living is tiring.
Just let them live their lives. Why do you have to take on their burdens?
Poor people like us should get together. All we have is ourselves.
What did Jung Hoon say to you?
He's very temperamental just like his mom.
Why is a rich family being so cheap?
Is marriage a business? If they have more money, they can spend more.
You'll be his family anyway.
Why do they care about profit and loss?
What are you doing?
Let me hug you for a while.
Don't worry though. I'll meet your mother-in-law again and work it out.
I said sorry after I talked back to you last time, didn't I?
It's not that important in our relationship.
I thought you were different from your mother.
But you're a lot like her.
Does she think a marriage is like a business
since she's doing the business?
Does she want to make a profit out of your marriage?
We had a fight every single day while preparing for the wedding.
I probably could endure it today, but not tomorrow
I can't take a road when I know what's going to happen.
You lied to me. You lied to me habitually.
You got back. I knew you'd come back by now.
I told you my password. You could've just come in. Why did you ring a bell?
This is a woman's house. I can't just barge in.
What are you doing?
- I need a dog.
- Why?
I saw in a movie that a Eskimo hugs
a dog when they sleep during cold days.
I'm so cold tonight.
How did your brother's funeral go?
Are you going to be a dog or not?
I can't be a dog unless I drink.
Do you know how radiant my brother was?
We were born from the same parents, but we were so different.
I was jealous of him the most.
But why did he die?
How much did Hae Yoon and Sang Jin love each other?
Oh my God. How can I lock up Mrs. Jung's mouth?
What a bad bastard!
You're so selfish!
Your suffering comes first before mine even at this moment.
I have nothing to say though.
At this moment, nothing will make you feel better.
If there's only one person that understands
you, you will never give up hope.
He had everything but why? Why?
Why didn't he have that one person?
There's this famous saying in China.
A man risks his life for a woman who acknowledges him.
A woman risks her life for a man who loves her.
You're so stupid. A woman puts make
up on for a man who loves her.
It was make up?
So a woman doesn't risk her life?
Anyway, my point is
it's hard to earn someone's heart.
A man will risk his life if a woman acknowledges him.
I had a chance to be that person.
I had a chance!
I did have a chance on that day!
Let's not pull out my hair.
You're so mean.
Don't risk your life, you bastard!
Don't do that.
Daddy.
Daddy!
I'll go there soon. I know. I'll be there soon.
Just send the patients to Dr. Yoon.
I'll do the surgery after I get there.
Be prepared.
- Do you have to go back to the hospital?
- Yeah.
I had so much fun. It was my
first time coming here with you.
Isn't it, Mom?
- We came here together before.
- Yeah, we did.
The reason why Mom and Dad came here with you is because we have something to tell you.
Honey, let's not start this way.
He's seven. He's exposed to TV and games.
Let's not make him confused.
Maybe what I was worried about is happening.
What did you worry about?
Are you going to die, Dad?
No wonder you were being nice to me.
No. He's not going to die, Tae Hyun.
- It's okay. Don't cry.
- You're lying.
It felt strange that you were being nice to me recently.
Give him to me. I'll do it.
You have to go to the hospital.
Just go open the door.
- It's your stuff.
- Did you pack them already?
It was my job to pack your stuff
when you went to the seminar
- It's not hard for me.
- Why are there two?
These are winter clothes so I
also packed clothes for the spring.
It's like you wanted me to leave a long time ago.
This is what you want.
Go now.
We didn't tell Tae Hyun that
we're getting a divorce.
I will do it. You saw how he reacted to it.
You weren't home a lot.
He wouldn't even notice you left.
- You can see him on weekends.
- Which one is the winter clothes?
This one.
I will only take this with me.
- What is this?
- Let me stay here for a while.
Hey, hey.
If there's a can beer, give me one.
Wasn't yesterday the trial?
Yeah. So I feel nasty now.
I told you to get a divorce by agreement.
Even that makes you feel nasty.
Here.
After the first trial with my first ex-wife,
she started to cry at the stairs.
She was the one who
wanted the divorce.
I wanted to cry but I tried not to.
I thought I'd feel less sad
with my second ex-wife.
But I felt exactly the same.
You can't get used to pain.
I miss my father.
He was a very strict person.
He was very busy studying every day.
If he had a free day, my mom didn't let me
play with him because he was tired.
Did you tell your parents about the divorce?
Not yet. I'm planning to go there next week.
I'm wondering how my father will react.
He didn't like this marriage anyway
so he'll probably be happy.
There's no possibility that Hae
Jin and you will get back together?
I think I'm done with her.
She looked like one of plaintiffs
for my malpractice suit.
- What's this?
- Let me stay here for a while.
- No.
- Why not? She almost killed me last night.
Let me just stay here for a while. She's very
stressed because of her daughter's divorce.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Then have fun but don't stay.
I came first.
Wow. I thought my sister was
going too far with the divorce.
Think whatever you want.
I suppose Mrs. Jung and I are the first
ones who found out about this.
Fights aren't allowed in this house.
I should go to my hospital now.
See you later, Min Ho.
Sure.
- You're going to eat dinner outside, right?
- Yeah.
- Is it me or him?
- What?
Who gets to stay here? Me or him?
You both can stay here.
How can I do that?
Is it me or that bastard?
Let's break up.
It hasn't been 24 hours
since we started dating.
I know. This was the shortest
relationship that I had.
I've forgotten what it was
like to date a woman.
And you're one of them. I hate
being forced to make a choice.
Can we not all live together?
Why did you slap me?
Don't tell me that kind of stuff so easily.
What's this?
Am I dating a clingy woman?
I think I fell in love with you
the moment I held your hand.
I won't force to make you a choice.
Do you still want to break up with me?
We did the holding hands step.
Next step is to kiss.
We did kiss.
That one doesn't count because
it was before we started dating.
You're so funny.
My head hurts because of the hangover.
- Are you not taking shower?
- I don't shower in the morning.
Do you plan to remain a virgin
until marriage or something?
It's the first time I didn't sleep
with a woman in a hotel.
I guess you come to hotels with women often.
It isn't the first time for you either.
Did you check my background?
Don't you know how small this circle is?
You dated so many men. I didn't want
to know but my friends told me that.
I'm not planning to remain a virgin until
marriage but I won't sleep with you.
I'm going to change my clothes.
Order some food for me.
Can we still order food in this time?
We can. I came here with
somebody this time.
I want a steak.
I don't love you either but
I have sense of kinship.
We both know this is
a marriage of convenience.
To maintain this marriage,
we should respect each other.
Coming to a hotel with women
is respecting me?
It's like you're hiding something.
I thought you'd tell me if I did first.
This is a marriage where we don't
have to share our secrets.
I don't want to know your secret.
I want to know what you're hiding.
Do you think only your friends
tell you about my past?
They tell me about your past too.
Don't you know how small this circle is?
If this is going to bother our
marriage, let's not do this marriage.
I'll tell my parents.
I think you're feeling got hurt. I guess
you're not a real business man.
You said marriage is a business.
You're calling off the marriage because of your assumption.
Sometimes, assumption can be more accurate than evidence.
Okay, I'll behave. I'd rather be a divorcee than break off an engagement.
Are you going to order me the steak?
What the hell are you?
There's only one goal for this marriage.
I want to be free from my family.
You also get help from your father
if you do this marriage.
It's win-win for us, is it not?
You order the food.
I'm going to take a shower.
Don't speak to me informally.
Let's follow the rule.
Sure. Could you order
food yourself please?
- Hey.
- Where are you?
- I'm still in a hotel.
- Can you not talk?
- Yes, I can. What is it?
- Dong Bi got back so don't worry.
Can you tell her that I'm worried about her?
No, I didn't. I didn't want her to suffer because of you.
What was her problem anyway?
Well, everyone thinks differently.
- Jung Hoon.
- My mom's here.
Why is she there?
I couldn't go home because
I slept at Dong Bi's house.
Okay.
Bye.
Even in business, you can have feelings.
I learned a lesson.
I think you have a bad habit.
Why do you sleep out?
Even if you're going to get
married, this isn't good.
You're guessing wrong.
I was at Dong Bi's house.
She was having a hard time
because of her family.
But still, you guys are a man and a woman.
Hae Yoon must be so happy to hear that.
Dong Bi is like my brother.
Hae Yoon understands that.
No, she doesn't.
You don't know about women.
Don't let her know. Even if Dong Bi is a
friend, I'd be upset.
You always butt your nose in my business.
And don't make things like this. It's tiring for you.
I had to go somewhere anyway.
I'm going to meet Hae Yoon's mom.
We're going to visit
the home we're getting you.
Did you say something bad about her
business when you were yelling at Hae Yoon?
Did she tell you about that already?
You did.
Okay.
Is that it? What did she say about that?
Hae Yoon didn't say anything.
Calm down.
You get mad whenever I say something.
Am I doing it for no reason?
I know there's reason. That's
why I'm not saying anything.
About the house...
The bride's side doesn't have to pay
for the interior design, right?
We're going to have to pay for that anyway.
I'm going to see if she's
mooching off me again.
I'll decide if I can trust you
or not after you solve this problem.
Why are you not saying anything?
Are you mad?
No.
You don't have to see me out.
- What are you thinking?
- Nothing.
If you ignore my mom, I'm never
going to forgive you.
You're lying.
You're thinking about something else.
What are you doing?
Hey?
Where are you going?
What's wrong?
- Please just kill me.
- Why? What's wrong?
You can call me stupid or something.
I can't live without Hae Yoon.
I can't see her getting hurt.
I can't stand that it's me
who hurts her feelings.
I know Mrs. Jung is rude, but you
don't have to be rude to her.
I can't believe you're doing this.
We can pay everything. Let's do that.
We have enough money.
What's wrong with paying everything.
We have enough.
Why did I give birth to you?
If I can, I want to turn back time.
You're a nice woman.
You don't judge people by money.
This is your work place. Get up.
What if people see you?
So I came to the corner.
Please, save my life.
Don't pick up the fight with Hae Yoon's mom.
Just do whatever she wants.
This is why she thinks you're so easy.
I'm counting on you.
You came at the appointed hour.
One's credit is very important
to people who do business.
I hate the way she talks.
I hope Hae Yoon didn't tell her about what I said to her.
Which floor is it?
People who lived here before didn't
take care of the house very well.
Now we agree on something.
I know.
How long has this apartment been around?
About ten years.
It has been long. What if the price goes
down, and they have to live here forever?
I knew she would say that.
Just because it's a new apartment,
doesn't mean everything is good.
The price depends on the location
and the condition of the house.
I think this one is okay. There might be a
sick house syndrome for a new apartment.
I heard there isn't sick house syndrome
if it's made in eco friendly materials.
You sure know about a lot of stuff.
That's why I could make a living without starving myself.
But not as much as you do.
I never heard of setting up
a budget for the marriage this way.
That was an idea I made up. It's obvious
that you never heard about it.
Would I think of this if it weren't that bad?
I think we will have to change the toilet too.
- We should fix everything, right?
- Yes.
We will have to make an estimate.
If they plan on having children, the interior shouldn't give off the aura of newlyweds.
I don't know how many babies they're having.
The baby might ruin the design anyway,
so don't spent too much money on interior design.
Do we have to pay for that again?
I should counterattack.
If you're done with the design, I'll buy furniture.
I feel so bad for making you pay all that.
So I'll buy furniture.
So you're only preparing the bottom drawer?
Mrs. Ha, humans are born,
and then the money comes.
If you care too much about money,
you'll miss the people around you.
It's like you're a real business woman.
You're good at calculating profit and loss.
Oh my God.
That's what I want to say.
You're so much better at calculating the profit and loss.
Before I came to see you, my son
said we should pay everything.
Because we have enough money.
Then listen to him.
I think he was right about that.
Love is what's most important.
If you want to show off yourself, do it. It's not that hard to listen.
I must've misunderstood.
I know you're not a materialistic person.
You don't judge people by money.
Of course I don't.
Since we're done discussing, let's go home.
Something went wrong.
- How are you going to go home?
- I can take a taxi.
I'll take you home. The gas
price is so high these days.
She's making a favor of it.
It's okay. I can take a taxi.
Why don't you drive?
I have a husband and son who can give
me a ride. Or I can take a taxi.
Even if they're your families, you
shouldn't rely on them too much.
They might get tired of it.
They're not your servants.
She's trying to teach me again.
The men in my life love to serve me.
Believe what want to believe.
Pardon?
You know what's good
after I lost my husband?
There is a good thing after
you lost your husband?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
To feed my kid, I can do anything.
There's nothing I can't take on.
That's why you're brazen. You need to have a sense of honor though.
What the heck?
- It's okay.
- No. They should learn a lesson.
That crazy bastard.
Hey, you bastard! Where did you
learn how to drive? You suck at it!
Are you laughing at me now?
You stop the car right now!
- I'll not get off.
- Sure. Bye.
Bye.
I can't beat her.
You said you're going to beat her up
this time. It didn't go well?
She drives so recklessly. I almost died.
I feel like it was some kind of warning
to be nice to her daughter or something.
She looks nice but she is pretty tough.
I'm going to beat her one day.
How?
I can't beat her physically but
I'm going to beat her verbally.
Is she that good of a speaker?
Yes, she is. She told me that humans
are born, and then comes the money.
That's what I should've said to her.
Why didn't I say that before?
My counterattack was good,
but the finish wasn't that good.
I tried to comfort myself by
thinking of Jung Hoon but I can't.
What did Jung Hoon say?
He told me to pay everything and
not to hurt Hae Yoon's feeling.
He said that because he has
to take responsibility.
But he's incompetent. I feel bad for him.
Please consider Hae Yoon's situation.
How?
Usually groom's parents should pay more.
Let's stop talking about it and find some
class so you can be a good speaker too.
- Let's win!
- I'm going to!
Your mother has given up.
Love Hae Yoon as much as you want.
I have something to say to you.
I'll meet you at your building.
Thank you for calling me first.
There is a lot to talk about.
Let's talk calmly.
Give these to your mom.
Mom doesn't need anything.
Don't buy stuff for her.
It's what my mom gave you.
I should give these to her, but
I'm not brave enough to see her.
What do you mean?
I want to break up with you.
It's not only you having a hard time.
Giving up like this makes all the
things we went through come to nothing.
- Did you know it snowed yesterday?
- Really?
It was the first snow of the year.
The first snow after we started
dating was like this too.
What do we do if we meet up these days?
We talked about what our mom
said about the wedding.
The most important thing for love is romance,
but that's gone.
There's only petty reality left.
This is the first reason
why we should break up.
The second reason is...
The second one is more
important than the first one.
All the insecurities that I've tried
to hide have started to come out.
Why am I not from a rich family?
Why isn't my mom elegant?
Why did my dad pass away so fast?
It gets worse if I see your parents.
I'm so jealous that your
parents get along well.
And I'm jealous of your mother's self-confidence.
I'm jealous of you because
they are your parents.
And I keep fighting with myself.
Saying, 'Jung Hae Yoon,
you're a great person.'
In that way, I try to assert my confidence.
I have to try.
I tell myself that I'm a worthy woman
because I have control over you.
Our love surrendered to reality.
Our love is making us weak, not strong.
I'm sorry that I pushed you to marry me.
You did push me, but in the end,
the choice was mine.
Don't be ridiculous. You're a great woman.
That's true.
You're just blaming yourself because
you're in a state of confusion.
I'll do better not to
make you think that way.
The third reason is...
This is the most important reason.
I love you.
If I think of you suffering because of me
it pains my heart.
I love you. I love you more than myself.
How can I see you getting hurt because of me?
This is a good chance to run away from me.
Don't do that. I'm a having hard time
being in the middle of all of this.
If we get married, we probably don't
have time to see your mother.
I need to see her.
I have sympathy for my mom.
Others might say bad things about her.
But I saw her life.
I saw what she went through.
I can't ignore her.
Okay. I'll be good to your mom.
Didn't you hear what I said so far?
I'm the problem not you.
Are you sure you won't regret it?
I'm not sure.
But I'm not going to come back.
Why are you crying then?
I'm not crying.
Okay. I won't cling to you anymore.
You said what we are left with is
petty reality. How can I stop you?
- She isn't home yet.
- The room will be sold soon, right?
I should see it first.
- Which room is it?
- It's this one.
Sell it to a woman that'd only sleep here.
I don't want her to drink a lot.
- Who is she?
- Don't bother.
Okay.
I'll call you later then.
- Bye.
- What was that?
- I put your room for sale.
Why did you do that?
What did I say?
I'm sorry, sis.
I knew you'd come back. He felt burdened
when you wanted to move in?
He looks so irresponsible!
Your taste in men is so bad.
- It's not that.
- Then what is it?
Somebody was in his house before I came.
- Is that a women?
- No, it was Do Hyun.
- He was there?
- Yeah.
How could I live there?
Sis, I have pride.
Make a choice. Are you going
to sell the motorcycle or not?
Are you going to?
This is how he felt.
Do I have to choose?
The third option is I convince
you to let me ride.
Shut up.
Are you going to sell it or not?
- I'll sell it.
- Are you going to date him or not?
Are you going to date him or not?
Do I really have to make a choice?
We can negotiate.
- Then get out!
- I'll not date him.
Your sister-in-law didn't
come for her skin care.
Call her and tell her to come.
He still cares about them even
if he's getting a divorce.
Tae Hyun, why did you think
Dad was going to die?
Grandma said if a person does something he
didn't before, then he's going to die soon.
I was so nervous because of him.
He's not going to die. He's very healthy.
He's going to protect you
until you're grown up.
- Tae Hyun.
- Yes?
I started off on the wrong button.
It looks funny.
It does, right? If you start off on the wrong button, it looks weird.
- What should I do then?
- You can unbutton it and do it again.
You're right.
Mom and Dad stepped off on the
wrong foot just like this button.
We both are going to start over
at different houses separately.
Are you guys splitting up?
Yeah. It's called a divorce.
Then what about me?
It's not going to be different for you.
You will live with me.
And Dad will come here to hang out with you.
So he was being nice to me
because he's getting a divorce?
He felt sorry that he didn't
get to hang out with you.
He can get a divorce if he comes here to play with me more often. I can still live with you.
My temperature shouldn't
be too high or too low.
- Why is that?
- Because hail can't be made.
You're good, honey.
Hello?
I want to speak to Tae Hyun.
I told him about us.
Tae Hyun, it's Dad.
- Dad.
- Hey, buddy.
- What were you doing?
- I was reading a book about hail.
- Tae Hyun, I'm not going to die.
- I know. I heard from Mom.
I'm going to spend more time with you now.
Could you go to a sledge park with me?
If you want, I'll take you anywhere.
I'm okay with a divorce.
So don't worry about me.
Okay, good night.
You too. I love you Daddy.
I learned this at kindergarten.
Okay. Good night.
You too.
I went to your marital house with Mrs. Ha.
I kind of yelled at Jung Hoon yesterday.
I told him to fix the problem, and his mom said
she will do the interior design for the house.
You still have the money that you borrowed
from the bank, right? Give it back to the bank.
All we have to do is buy furniture.
We can buy them with money I have.
Listen to me.
What's wrong?
You didn't even have dinner.